buklao: Supp
SKPTCL: ahoy m8
thefacultyof: sup
jay_al97: hello @georgehotz
allthesm0ke: Where's the prank Hotz?
thefacultyof: what are your plans today
allthesm0ke: You have 2 hours left if you're in PST/MST
lightofhel1: yo
E_Pizza: effHi geo love ur coding big fan
FalconJet_: sup george
shr3knad0: Hype
jay_al97: i was just watching an old video
lonez: YOOOO
sfmoose: Leeeeets Goooooo!
tahecs89: hello everyone
samwilliamson7: What’s going on George
shr3knad0: I love comma.ai it’s honestly insane
sfmoose: I qira’d hard last night, thanks for the dockerfile
SKPTCL: Use comma ai equity to acquire pure leaf?
buklao: Pfff only spindrifts are allowed
shr3knad0: Do you like the new stack overflow
Cube_Is_Life20: George what are some not so intermediate level projects to do? and should I always use a libraries or write my own?
buklao: You still own shares in comma right
alienware997: Greetings from Germany! 7am in the morning here but perfectly just woke up
sfmoose: What reading material should I read to become proficient with debuggers and qira?
siggb: How is your instagram?
sfmoose: 9-5s are a scam
allthesm0ke: REDIS BABY
buklao: So you're erlich bochman of your company nice
Toaster_PG: teach me java pls
buklao: Java is a shit language
buklao: Libtards made it
Toaster_PG: y
chase_higgins: yo George you quit?
lightofhel1: sudo?
buklao: It's slow and id rather use rust
ScrubLifeChoseMe: eyyy
Cube_Is_Life20: instagrambot-py is a great library on github I got 200 followers in a week with it.... too bad George only wants organic growth
shutchie: Memcached?
ScrubLifeChoseMe: commai Pog
chase_higgins: George how do I join the church?
Adriasian: says 90
ScrubLifeChoseMe: bro u got 90
canardppc: what's your name on linkedin mate ?
FalconJet_: says 90 on my end
ScrubLifeChoseMe: and its only been 5 minutes c
chase_higgins: @canardppc it's George Hotz lmaooo
skout23: AWS dynamodb too expensive?
Erichmoraga: It's pretty late, George. People like to sleep.
dorkmo: filecoin
shutchie: @skout23 wants local I think
Adriasian: papa george
canardppc: well can't ind him, maybe bc i'm french, i don't know
Cube_Is_Life20: George it's fucking late 10pm eastern 1am western
Adriasian: golang baby
chase_higgins: now working for Church of the New Hackers
wilderel: yo when are you putting more shit on soundcloud
anudeepgi: but early morning in India :)
buklao: Lawl types "verbose"
wilderel: much love from your ROomanian boys
Adriasian: sudo kiss me
shr3knad0: 10:45 is not early in the morning
shr3knad0: This incident will be reported
Toaster_PG: hows ur instagram doing
sfmoose: My cat is #27
FalconJet_: hey george, do you like the touch bar when dev'ing on laptop or nah?
anudeepgi: PogChamp PogChamp
shr3knad0: Kappa
Prest0n1337: What are you workin on tonight?
onu4r: I bet he can't reach 1 M by the end of the year
sfmoose: You’re 1% the way to your Instagram goal. We believe in you.
KrakkenTM: does he read chat?
Prest0n1337: not really
zeccran: @georgehotz do you know how to get user input in 32 bit protected mode of a booatloader?
chase_higgins: George when's your bed time? lmao it's so late
Ahxs: yooo
chase_higgins: like 10 pm man
buklao: It's 1:17 am
rvggggg: ghnghh
Prest0n1337: I understand
jay_al97: I do
i_am_sneaky: yo
KrakkenTM: not me
Prest0n1337: You just dont' explain much bro
chase_higgins: we got you george
rvggggg: wait it isnt subscriber only chat? :)
wilderel: no one bro
SteveATZ: because we like watching you work
thefacultyof: im just here to see smartman do code word
zeccran: I like learning things from you, may not be my focus, but i learn new things
buklao: I care
lightofhel1: qira is love
wilderel: what the fuck is this shit code minecraft 2
thefacultyof: this dude disses his audience too much
shutchie: <<
shr3knad0: Kappa
arisnotle: I enjoy this shit
Prest0n1337: I been doing learning on writing STM firmwares and doing C
buklao: How you structure your projects is in my interests
SKPTCL: We care but we aren't all at your level
thermalterm2: never do meetups man
thefacultyof: oh man yourself, pal
i_am_sneaky: twitch slam was legit
wilderel: did you invite the bots in bangladesh?
KrakkenTM: @georgehotz whats your keyboard?
sfmoose: Django might be a better choice if this is something that needs to be async and production quality
CamBaiL: LUL
sfmoose: Or flask async
chase_higgins: did anyone claim that cash?
Toaster_PG: clean room = new man
Cube_Is_Life20: George can you explain what a "key value store" like if you need to save a value just edit a file?
Prest0n1337: I think most of the people who know who you are are the people in the live coding crowd
i_am_sneaky: right? piano gone? wtf
rvggggg: i can only code python am i a lame ?
Erichmoraga: It's interesting to see how George thinks. Dissing the audience is fine, folks.
i_am_sneaky: yes
sfmoose: Me
Prest0n1337: Or folks who've seen you on G4 back in the day when they showcased you
buklao: Yell mother f*ck and it'll work
Prest0n1337: bout the Sony stuffs
vaporwave_memes: I miss G4
sfmoose: We’re also here for the rants
Prest0n1337: I love the rant about contributing nothing
Prest0n1337: explains my life
goolulusaurs: A lot of the best twitch streamers are really good a commentary too while they are playing games. I think it would help a lot if you talked/explained more as you were going so people could keep up and follow along more easily.
Level_002: im here for the VIM orgasm
sfmoose: Lemme guess, introverted nerds on insta?
Prest0n1337: hilarious
buklao: Lmao it's a scam
alienware997: Im here to learn and because you entertain...right now studying IT, second semester so i can follow you for around 80% of the time @georgehotz
KrakkenTM: stop fkin complaining and keep streamin
KrakkenTM: stianHaha stianHaha
Ahxs: Front end Web developer PogChamp
sfmoose: We’re hear to ask what keyboard you use every 10 mins
SKPTCL: What do you want your viewers to be like
i_am_sneaky: @goolulusaurs bro you ever try explaining shit as you code? Shit gets hard a few hundred lines in
Adriasian: blinkxFood
Cube_Is_Life20: who wants to explain to what a key value store is and why it's not just just stored in a text file?
thefacultyof: like its not like everyone is going to be even remotely familiar with the project
shutchie: Logs
wilderel: when are the hot chicks arriving geohotz?
i_am_sneaky: @Cube_Is_Life20 google does bro
OArtero: are you saying that in a MTG with instagram you saw that your audience don't know what are you coding?
Adriasian: what are we using the key-value store for
Prest0n1337: I think he's lacking screen real estate and doesn't read our chat much
bakztfuture: is flask debug mode on?
Cube_Is_Life20: @i_am_sneaky im on mobile I'm not trying to leave the stream to Google that shit
SGK7: Nah he only listens to subs @prest0n1337
Prest0n1337: Waiting for my twitch prime to hit it said on the 2nd so any minute
Prest0n1337: The whole talk only to subs bs though won't win people over
i_am_sneaky: 2019 you cant multitask on mobile?
goolulusaurs: @i_am_sneaky No, I bet it is hard, and I know even with games a lot of streamers have trouble talking while they play, I guess its just a skill you gotta practice.
bastianbeps: hi
Prest0n1337: thats like people who sit and wait for donos
Ahxs: That’s a sick UI
Prest0n1337: How's the last project you streamed going?
Cube_Is_Life20: @i_am_sneaky lmao yeah I got it
Prest0n1337: By the way @georgehotz nice hair cut
Level_002: this guy is limited by the mac. Need some windows or linux on his life.
Prest0n1337: I like better when you look like Bob Ross's lost son
maruchandayo: hi
maruchandayo: HeyGuys HeyGuys
Prest0n1337: I like seeing you program though George seening other experienced people actually showing how much they use reference docs instead of pretending to be a unicorn who knows everything
maruchandayo: sanic is also very fast
sfmoose: He had Linux servers he sshs into frequently. Plus docker and rendering farms, he’s not limited by a Mac.
Prest0n1337: I'll hit you with my Prime sub I think I have to wait like another 30min
un3okapi: sonic the hedgehog
thefacultyof: Kappa
Bloodspark_: really LUL
TimmyName: I don't think a lot of these people realize who george is
onu4r: dude there's also FASTAPI
onu4r: it's new but great
cjoelrun: aiohttp fast
maruchandayo: sanic is not that bad. i'm using it on production without any issues.
jocal17: who george is?
Prest0n1337: Well correct me if i'm wrong others helped George but he got most of the public recognition over the lawsuit
Toaster_PG: george == god
Level_002: Entrepreneur son of Tony Stark @jocal17
Cube_Is_Life20: I'd like to see George write his own api framework that'd be some real entertainment
Prest0n1337: you could write an API but api framework not sure what that is supposed to be
Level_002: @Prest0n1337 ehhhhhhhmm... example Slim Framework
TimmyName: DarkMode
Smithygmx: hes typing so fast
SKPTCL: give me mod
SKPTCL: ill clean this up
dorkmo: oh hey
maruchandayo: @fraudulentfarmer both of em is shit
funwayz: LMAO
Prest0n1337: George can you time me out
sfmoose: Bitches love env vars
Erichmoraga: Stay focused.
Prest0n1337: I can't talk to these idiots
Hexybu: purge drxPog
leond53: LOL
SKPTCL: Thank you sir
MrBankster: WOW
alienware997: Here want mod too:D
Ahxs: ban hammer George coming in hot PogChamp
Cube_Is_Life20: that's the George we know and love
Level_002: nice
TimmyName: alienware997 wants mod
MrBankster: george i am really into your beard
TimmyName: python3
TimmyName: ban me
lithiumx4900: I like the frequent streaming times. It's hard to find consistent programming streams
maruchandayo: @lithiumx4900 the best stream is here boi
Prest0n1337: i'm doing learning on ARM M4 tonight so i'm drinking a pot of coffee it was that or bleach so if I talk to much
syska: you have 127:0:0:1 viewers sir :D
Prest0n1337: thats my excuse
mrpentakills: You are insane with vim my man. Saw some video of yours yesterday and realized you are on twitch. How long have you been here? Glad you are here anywho.
maruchandayo: SeemsGood
lithiumx4900: I live in LA. Sorry about the traffic in advance
Prest0n1337: I can hook you up with Paul Denino
MrBankster: la >> sf
TimmyName: bruh that rap you made back in the day fire
Prest0n1337: I actually can tho
sfmoose: Make us proud
Prest0n1337: Yo it's geohot for those who don't know
Prest0n1337: I guess i'm a nerd for knowing the first line
Prest0n1337: fml
sfmoose: If only there was a way to analyze the binary
Cube_Is_Life20: @sfmoose kek
Prest0n1337: well you'd wanna analyze in hex
Ahxs: Double os import Kreygasm
lightofhel1: double import os btw
z0di4ckx: YOOOOOO!
syska: import os OmegaLul
cjoelrun: I use docker compose for env stuff
Cube_Is_Life20: gotta import it twice just to be sure lmao
maruchandayo: lol
Zealeigh: That jumper is fucking with my OCD
Prest0n1337: for that person who asked how to get started in RE there is Ghidra and lots of new tutorials on the topic
Prest0n1337: just check out youtube
fa_k: what is he actually working on?
Prest0n1337: hey key value store he explained part of it a sec ago
sk84uhlivin: I really enjoyed your SXSW presentation George ^_^
Cube_Is_Life20: @fa_k database stuff
syska: i hate mongo
TimmyName: yeah the SXSW
Prest0n1337: I started to watch it but from what I gathered in the first few mins if we are talking about the same talk seemed a bit of a odd talk
Prest0n1337: maybe I stopped to early
fa_k: @Cube_Is_Life20 oh ok
fa_k: python stopped working monkaS
Zealeigh: If python forks does it become medusa?
sfmoose: I’m here for the jetskis
Toaster_PG: cool... but can you code minecraft in 1 week??
Cube_Is_Life20: can't fork = he writes his own version of leveldb
jagger_rsw: but python sxxxss, rust rulez
poobum999: BCWarrior
TimmyName: good mods
shutchie: Memcached
jagger_rsw: Also, why are we looking at puting to and getting pieces of text out of files. Gerge, why won't you program AGI live instead? :)
sfmoose: Nginx is god
abhinavneelam: Everyone follow @georgehotz instagram
dorkmo: inception key value store
dorkmo: a key within a key
th3_maj0r: yoyo
dorkmo: yooo
poobum999: yo DogFace
th3_maj0r: are you drinking jack daniels?!?
nizero: sup george
redeagle1881: I like your terminal set up, have you got your dotfiles up on github or something?
nizero: i watched your sxsw talk, it was pretty good
th3_maj0r: @redeagle1881 yes
redeagle1881: @th3_maj0r on the /geohot gh account?
th3_maj0r: yes
Cube_Is_Life20: check out HyperLevelDB or substack level-party they may help with your leveldb problem?
Knarez: LUL
vybhavb: Hello!
aMulisha: LUL
Quad___lol: lmao
nizero: loll
aMulisha: It's Y2K bro
ab289528: 4Head
2knucklechamp: I dont think thats april fools either lol
Quad___lol: i remember when internet was an anonymous place FeelsBadMan
Quad___lol: @georgehotz what do you think of Tery Davis! do you think you can compete with him?
2knucklechamp: What is he trying to build? The title didn’t make much sense to me.
zutchbell: an hashmap probably?
josalt: Hey everyone
TimmyName: ban that quad guy
Adriasian: very cool
ab289528: oh got it
Cube_Is_Life20: so it's just a database with 2 columns?
Lazysloth: what keyboard is that
trashcan___: hhkb
2knucklechamp: Lol yeah that keyboard sounds hackerman
ab289528: ^
Cube_Is_Life20: @quad___lol Terry Davis was a schizo who was stuck in the 90's George is easily on par with him
kougithings: @Lazysloth If you get the same keyboard your programming skills will increase by 30%!
Lazysloth: so 0 x 1.3
th3_maj0r: sub the channel increase ur skill by 35%
th3_maj0r: sub > keyboard
Cube_Is_Life20: @kougithings same thing happens if you switch from atom to vim
Lazysloth: spacemacs, with vi bindings
reverseIRA: ugh! i still stuck on visual code with hundreds extension BibleThump
2knucklechamp: I wanna learn vim
2knucklechamp: Python in vscode makes me want to kick a baby
Lazysloth: they got vi bindings in vscode
reverseIRA: yep
kougithings: @cube_is_life20: I tried out vim, couldn't figure out how to quit it. Now I have stockholm syndrome.
zutchbell: i prefer atom
Lazysloth: its !letmeout
ab289528: @kougithings 4Head
mudmud17: !time
reverseIRA: my mentor said that using vim make u discipline
Lazysloth: in russia vim disciplines you
AFROH4CK: they should
m0etaz: is this the new Redis?
pau1riddle: Yo, George!
th3_maj0r: 119 viewers
josalt: You are popular George!
joker2k999: Lol
Lazysloth: how many lines do we have left
ab289528: you are
Bombapil0t: 9.942 > 9000 PogChamp
pau1riddle: Comments and blank lines usually don't count.
MrVehe: You're popular, but in spain it's 8:30 am, NOBODY IS AWAKEN TO THIS TIME.
joker2k999: Lol
Lazysloth: MrVehe aren't you though?
ab289528: 3am here in brazil
RaketenTier: not Popular? LOL. Suecase with Sony. Kicking Teslas ass...
abhinavneelam: @georgehotz why don’t you keep posting on insta?
th3_maj0r: 8.30 here too
MrVehe: I'm working, that doesn't count :) @Lazysloth
Lazysloth: georgehotz only posts on tinder
bourbaki77: I like listening to you hack while I work on my abstract algebra homework B)
iHench: %s/tinder/grindr
pau1riddle: @bourbaki77 I was reading Algebra: Chapter 0
trashcan___: append only >> delete
pau1riddle: @bourbaki77 best book on abstract algebra
bourbaki77: Is. that the one that blends in category theory?
pau1riddle: yeah
Lazysloth: yo i think his hoodie is insideout...
pau1riddle: it's not for newbies though
bourbaki77: Nice! I tried but I was still to much of a noob
Lazysloth: probably doesn't even wash his hoodie, just turns it insideout
Lazysloth: lifehax
bourbaki77: We are using Shifrin
enlightenedwaterfowl: Don't forget to support PATCH
Lazysloth: can't you make a script to run a test on ur server instead of running the command repeatedly
abhinavneelam: I think he said it didn’t work because of an environment variable or something and that it had to be a command line variable
enlightenedwaterfowl: The strongest trees grow in the harshest winds
ericswenson15: Micro service
ericswenson15: Rip monoliths
v0lko: what's wrong with consul?
Lazysloth: your mom is a monolith
joker2k999: Lol
Ni3uS: @georgehotz hey.. could you write some kind of a code, that can help me find my real mother?
risky_banana: I'm subscribed and I don't wanna say shit like that
joker2k999: I never worked with ngnx
bourbaki77: my god it's full of stars
Bombapil0t: :D
Bombapil0t: good ppl subscribe on twitch and follow on instagram. don't forget guys
joker2k999: Gotta re-factor bro
Lazysloth: did he say what this kv was for?
yamesboard: just joined, what are we building?
Grimonja: Or volume server registers with master on boot
joker2k999: I see we back in tmux boys
poobum999: monkaS
joker2k999: Lol
Bombapil0t: haha
Lazysloth: i thought a cat was on his desk when he tsk tsk
MrBankster: TDD?
ab289528: hahaha
joker2k999: Gotta be subscribed bro. Everyone knows this.
pau1riddle: But if you want to change code, you have to change tests. The more tests you have, the more difficult it is to change code.
th3_maj0r: yes
MrBankster: i like space seperated lists, like in clojure
jay_al97: pass it a set
enlightenedwaterfowl: ;)
Bombapil0t: type speed like a sewing machine
Cube_Is_Life20: do you still do bounty hunting?
joker2k999: Yea when he’s not shilling for the gram
enlightenedwaterfowl: I honestly forget the semantics. Most people get it wrong though. I don't think it's necessarily true that one is meant to be idempotent
enlightenedwaterfowl: (I'd have to dig around myself)
pau1riddle: Bountry hunting is low leverage position, better become a full-fledged security consultant, that eat scraps from bug bounties.
enlightenedwaterfowl: PUT vs POST, yeah
joker2k999: you haven't had a rant in a while bro. U feeling ok? lol
jay_al97: are on the side of making software now that you're done with breaking software?
Lazysloth: you can't break what is already broken
enlightenedwaterfowl: -H "content-type: text/plain" ?
enlightenedwaterfowl: Didn't read the full args lis tactually
enlightenedwaterfowl: Yeah you probably want to specify content type via curl
Cube_Is_Life20: please be a one stream project. I unironically don't want to sleep tonight
TimmyName: I'm glad I subbed to have access to your VODs, because I'm lost currently
enlightenedwaterfowl: oh nvm, saw the request body
sam_disgusting: ASMR 10 hours of rhythmic spaghetti code key tapping to fall asleep to | MOST RELAXING (10:00:04)
Knarez: are you wearing your hoodie inside-out
th3_maj0r: twitch app use white text on white background?? wtf is this
TimmyName: get betterTTV
TimmyName: dark mode
TimmyName: android
th3_maj0r: on the mobile app?
Cube_Is_Life20: my chat reloaded but whoever mentioned the hoodie, he's probably hiding (((their))) logo
joker2k999: something IS better than nothing
wall_streeter: should one use python over php for web dev? if yes, why? Thank you!
joker2k999: python / (everything) = gucciGang
Varicode: Past broadcasts behind sub wall now :(
TimmyName: jsut sub
Varicode: Wonder if they'll still be posted to YT
Varicode: Yea most likely will
wall_streeter: @joker2k999 , why? :D
Varicode: Just noticed that wasn't the case some time ago
Knarez: LUL
Yaak0v: weird flex
joker2k999: but apparently only py3 because if you use py2 your a degenerate
nevroje: LUL
joker2k999: but ok..
wall_streeter: @joker2k999 LUL
wall_streeter: @joker2k999 but still, why?
joker2k999: i don't make the rules` bro
wall_streeter: @joker2k999 you just follow them? :( Are you a government employee or smth?
Lazysloth: man the gov is rich, they got funds to infiltrate a twitch stream
HoodedCloak: I watched your video interview. Super Hacker George Hotz: I Can Make Your Car Drive Itself for Under $1,000 and I just wanted to tell you that you remind me of Dr. Rodney McKay from Stargate: Atlantis and he was my favorite character. You have the same mannerisms, especially in that view interview.
enlightenedwaterfowl: High praise
HoodedCloak: Video interview*
Varicode: @HoodedCloak <3
HoodedCloak: :)
joker2k999: lol, bigSwag return is always good.
Varicode: LUL
th3_maj0r: ahahah
ericswenson15: You don’t like point and click editor?
Keyyyz: hell yea got to catch a stream
joker2k999: more or less being inflammatory ..
joker2k999: time out hammer incoming. lol
HoodedCloak: Dr. Rodney McKay was an absolute genius of the Stargate universe.
ericswenson15: That’s cool
HoodedCloak: So that's why people are saying it's high praise, probably.
Varicode: LUL
ericswenson15: You prefer it?
joker2k999: lol!
ericswenson15: Lol i never know what to do next while I’m actually building, so I draw out plans sometimes
Cube_Is_Life20: has geroge done any projects like his own os or browser? I'd download those in a snap
ericswenson15: And then build to that
ericswenson15: Then I can get a bunch of iterations on the plans
ericswenson15: Low coupling is everything
ericswenson15: Based on what I’ve read
lbucci3: - what problem r u trying to solve?
ericswenson15: For testing
ericswenson15: For refactoring
ericswenson15: Pub sub drastically reduces coupling
ericswenson15: You don’t seem coupled to any framework that is good
enlightenedwaterfowl: There are other messaging patterns beyond pub/sub, but yeah, decoupling is a good idea
ericswenson15: Yeah
ericswenson15: Scatter gather
ericswenson15: Coupling is where you have low dependency between components
Varicode: BIGSWAG
ericswenson15: It’s small functionality
joker2k999: trying to solve whether to more work later, or less work now...
joker2k999: *do
ericswenson15: It’s the same reason microservice is better than monolith
ericswenson15: It means you can easily pull apart code
ericswenson15: So less than 20 line functions
ericswenson15: Short files
ericswenson15: These thing naturally enforce low coupling
ericswenson15: Single imports in segregated files
enlightenedwaterfowl: Looks like 409 is a good status code for already-exists ("Conflict")
ericswenson15: That provides sing point of reliance
toolegit2quit_: watching ads for you george.
aresfour: george, did you go to uni?
joker2k999: lol, not sure if i like any enough to watch adds for em.
ericswenson15: The opposite of low coupling is a single file with every import and 1 function doing everything
ericswenson15: Long function and file names also reinforce low coupling
enlightenedwaterfowl: I dunno about that one
ericswenson15: Because specificity naturally introduces a need to separate functionality
pau1riddle: I saw some madmen disable hjkl in vim. So that they use / sor navigation.
ericswenson15: Robert Martin recommends 5 to 6 word variable names
enlightenedwaterfowl: I'd take that with a grain of salt
pau1riddle: Martin is a scam
ericswenson15: So idk but I extended that to file names
joker2k999: haven't used vim is so long...
ericswenson15: Yeah idk it’s just what I read
itsyaboyegg: as someone new to programming, is learning vim useful?
ericswenson15: The author of testable JavaScript says low coupling is the best way to combat untestable code
fowlmoves: what type of keys are those?
pau1riddle: %s/start_response/sr/g
fowlmoves: @itsyaboyegg its completely optional
ericswenson15: Iright
ericswenson15: Your pref
Lazysloth: itsyaboyegg if you are new to programming you have bigger problems then learning vim, but eventually it will be useful
ericswenson15: I use atom which is really nice
fowlmoves: @itsyaboyegg IDE will do just fine, just as emacs would
itsyaboyegg: is there any advantage learning it?
ericswenson15: Yeah
joker2k999: learning everything is useful. what not to learn.... theres a start...
ericswenson15: Robert Martin says your terminal is like your workbench
Lazysloth: cool story
ericswenson15: But I like atom because it helps me mentally
ericswenson15: Yeah idk lol
joker2k999: until they turn off your power..
Cube_Is_Life20: I think you forgot to change one of your start response's
izhosrs: hey @georgehotz can you send me a self driving car?
fowlmoves: @itsyaboyegg there isnt any inherent advantage to knowing vim, other than being useful when you remote into almost any *nix machine
Lazysloth: well there is more advantages then just remoting, its a great editor
fowlmoves: DELETE should retuen just headers. no?
fowlmoves: return*
fowlmoves: Optional body
aresfour: 204 no content
Harm133: thats what she said KAPPA
itsyaboyegg: @fowlmoves cool, thanks for the input
ericswenson15: Coupling is the boundary where you say, if I change this I also have to change this
ericswenson15: So you want to introduce boundaries between those two pieces of code
Harm133: what are we building a key value store for ?
ericswenson15: Because if each has a different rate of change
joker2k999: a bunch of SR. programmers use vim.
fowlmoves: Yeah API interface boundaries
ericswenson15: Then you can minimize on adjustments
joker2k999: since emacs i haven't looked back. still can't write lisp to save my life. lol
ericswenson15: An api with lots of function implies low coupling
enlightenedwaterfowl: Redis is great
ericswenson15: And yes that apis exist
joker2k999: go Redis bro.
pau1riddle: People say Redis is already pretty minimalist.
enlightenedwaterfowl: It is
ericswenson15: An api decouples your app from the api functionality
Lazysloth: !uptime
fowlmoves: It is very minimalist
Lazysloth: rip no bot
fowlmoves: But has most features you need
ericswenson15: High coupling means it would be hard to swap out your db
enlightenedwaterfowl: Yes it is
ericswenson15: Low coupling means you could switch in any db
enlightenedwaterfowl: Redis is highly configurable. You can put it into append-only file mode and maxmemory = 0, it's a quite different service at this point
enlightenedwaterfowl: Can be as reliable or unreliable as you want
ericswenson15: Highly configurable is good apparently
enlightenedwaterfowl: Did George Martin say that?
Lazysloth: burn
0TestUser: close to the 10 k on insta :D
ericswenson15: The author of tao of microservices says you should build so the app is highly configurable
pkacprzak: is posting link to AI/CV app I've recently published on reddit fine in chat? I'd like to get your opinion
ericswenson15: And yes lol he also says it
ericswenson15: George Martin says to build from configurable functional requirements
foxubu: The warmest greetings from Germany :)
ericswenson15: Though with microservices that mayb be harder
Lazysloth: ericswenson15 change your name to GMsays
ericswenson15: I suppose you could use a dashboard
foxubu: What? Python 2? :o
ericswenson15: Haha
ericswenson15: You first
joker2k999: lol
ericswenson15: Idk
foxubu: Oh sorry. Just the docs
joker2k999: gonna miss py2..
ericswenson15: Uber switched to microservice
ericswenson15: One exec wrote a book
enlightenedwaterfowl: (FWIW geohot, Redis definitely backs up to disk, per configuration)
ericswenson15: Def from a non dev perspective
ericswenson15: But really insightful
ericswenson15: She says chaos testing is the most inportant test for microservices
ericswenson15: So random extreme tests
ericswenson15: Like high load
enlightenedwaterfowl: Yeah she's probably wrong
Cube_Is_Life20: @pkacprzak no? he's not doing code reviews atm
ericswenson15: Or simulate failed service
ericswenson15: Lol idk
enlightenedwaterfowl: "Chaos" testing is not useless but it's not "the most important"
ericswenson15: Oh ok thanks
ericswenson15: What is most important?
pkacprzak: @Cube_Is_Life20 I meant for chat, not George
ericswenson15: Regression is what I do
ericswenson15: Integration is hard for me
enlightenedwaterfowl: "Chaos" testing is something you do when you're massive company like Netflix, Uber, whatever, and people are actually depending on your infrastructure
ericswenson15: Right
enlightenedwaterfowl: It's not something you need to worry about until you're an engineer at Uber
ericswenson15: You’re smart
ericswenson15: Haha
ericswenson15: Is the whole world moving to microservice?
ericswenson15: Where I work it is
ericswenson15: Apparently it reduces developer ego
ericswenson15: Because it’s not 1 person building the whole app
ericswenson15: It’s a bunch of teams
ericswenson15: Makes for more pleasant people lol
enlightenedwaterfowl: The thing is, it doesn't really matter. "Microservice" is just a pattern for structuring programs. It doesn't necessarily make anything better or worse
ericswenson15: At Uber they measure microservice quality by availability
kanogger: will we hit 10.000 today?
ericswenson15: They us 9’s
ericswenson15: So 99% availability
ericswenson15: Vs 99.9%
ericswenson15: So getting Dow to the actual seconds
ericswenson15: Lol
Varicode: PepoG
ericswenson15: That’s bug
ericswenson15: Big
ericswenson15: That’s a macroservice
joker2k999: you can doo it bro
ericswenson15: But I don’t worry about number of lines til I’m done building
ericswenson15: I go back and break apart
Jiggletoes: if it works u eat ass
ericswenson15: But I do use tiny functions that are extremely explicit
ericswenson15: Robert marring says no arguments to a function is best
ericswenson15: Followed by 1
enlightenedwaterfowl: No arguments means it's probably a side effect
enlightenedwaterfowl: Which is actually the worst
ericswenson15: And it gets exponentially worse as you add arguments
enlightenedwaterfowl: Please take everything you read with a grain of salt
ericswenson15: Because each implies additional coupling
joker2k999: tabs looks like my browser when I'm trying to remember the pip update command..
ericswenson15: Yeah I have no clue
ericswenson15: But reading is insane
ericswenson15: It’s like better than a whole year of coding
ericswenson15: No joke
ericswenson15: Good job on your function length @georgehotz
SGK7: Ppl appreciate what u have to say but ur sounding like an evangelist now
enlightenedwaterfowl: Pretty sure this guy is a high-level troll
ericswenson15: This other book recommends learning a language a month
ericswenson15: Haha sorry I’m a troll
joker2k999: update that py3 bro
joker2k999: lol
alienware997: alienware997 is gifting 1 Tier 1 Subs to georgehotz's community! They've gifted a total of 1 in the channel!
alienware997: alienware997 gifted a Tier 1 sub to Harm133!
Harm133: Pog
alienware997: ;)
Harm133: Thanks mate :D
Harm133: Mate Im the best
joker2k999: a lotta love in the chat bro's
enlightenedwaterfowl: This eric gentleman is a high-level troll
alienware997: i randomly gifted to somebody so...as long as its not eric:D
Harm133: haha
enlightenedwaterfowl: Thanks @alienware997
Lazysloth: they need to reneg a sub option lol
Harm133: do we get any emotes?
MrSnoopDog: mac so clean
enlightenedwaterfowl: Can you ignore people on this Twitch thing?
Lazysloth: yes i blocked him a couple min ago
enlightenedwaterfowl: geohot: Redis uses disk
kanogger: nice didn't know that, thanks
alienware997: alienware997 gifted a Tier 1 sub to Lazysloth! They have given 2 Gift Subs in the channel!
enlightenedwaterfowl: Thanks
Harm133: LUL
Jiggletoes: lmao
Varicode: LUL
kanogger: PogChamp
joker2k999: LOL
RomanNYC: LUL
Lazysloth: wow thanks alienware997 :D i can talk shit now
anatoly1974: how many languages do u code with @georgehotz
joker2k999: so you'll show up at.... 9:05?
kanogger: rip
joker2k999: damn... that power tho..
joker2k999: lol
Varicode: Wait why did we ban @ericswenson15
Cube_Is_Life20: @anatoly1974 he uses python3 for everything he can
Varicode: George was engaging with him about the code
joker2k999: because people sometimes don't like enthusiasm
Varicode: :/
Jiggletoes: george hotz long weiner
Knarez: could you use a lock
waterpringles: handsome
alienware997: @joker2k999 espacilly when somebody spams. i mean no Problem to write more and often but for every sentence a new meesage? so i'm fine with that:)
alienware997: alienware997 gifted a Tier 1 sub to Cube_Is_Life20! They have given 3 Gift Subs in the channel!
joker2k999: i figured George was gonna make him sub if he wanted to spam like that.
Harm133: since Im a sub now and you answer sub questions, what do you think about go ? @georgehotz
Jiggletoes: so many gifts why
Lazysloth: i like go's mascot that's about it :D.
giovannag: Why not :D
joker2k999: lol
Lazysloth: oh gofmt is cool too
pau1riddle: I remember George said about Go, it was "disgustingly verbose".
Harm133: :)
joker2k999: i think you use what you know best/first then port...
alienware997: im a little bit languid....or maybe im just friendly and like to make a gift to somebody. And when the gift is also helping this entertaining guy in this black box on my desktop gg:D
Cube_Is_Life20: oh sgiz I just looked at chat thanks for the gift
alienware997: np:)
Harm133: host immortal.local
Harm133: /etc/hosts
JumpTwiice: what keyboard is this?
kougithings: @jumptwiice: probably a HHK
joker2k999: dang, i gotta use 3/4 my screen to actually read whats goingz on
Harm133: I contributed to opensource Pog
JumpTwiice: PagChomp
mmmmmgrayonss: PogChamp
ericswenson15: Sorry what was I banned for?
enlightenedwaterfowl: Trolling. Stop trolling
ericswenson15: Oh ok sorry
enlightenedwaterfowl: Oh
JumpTwiice: Oh
ericswenson15: What dB you guys like?
andreas_bylund: oh
jay_al97: urlopen is easy
ericswenson15: Oh
ericswenson15: I read MySQL has nore accuracy?
alienware997: anybody interested in an indian ctf? Should run since two hours now and its organized by the Computer Science Departement of University of Delhi. check ctftime when you're interested in helping me)
ericswenson15: Have you guys tried multiple dbs?
Cube_Is_Life20: ay the instagrambot-py library I used uses requests
ericswenson15: What are we building?
ericswenson15: Nice
giovannag: @Cube_Is_Life20 Is that a bad thing?
ericswenson15: What does it do?
Cube_Is_Life20: @ericswenson15 comments, follows, likes, etc. @giovannag no I just thought it was interesting
JumpTwiice: LUL
Harm133: LUL
PeterBensch: PeterBensch subscribed with Twitch Prime.
Varicode: LUL
joker2k999: LOL. oh wow bro
alienware997: Twitch Prime is free!
myaocat: YouWHY
joker2k999: LOL.
pau1riddle: He is a stalker
andreas_bylund: LUL
Varicode: Tfw Preston tries to work for comma but forgets he has to get into google first
mmmmmgrayonss: ya yeet
KhaosVFX: esketit
myaocat: ba
geobitz: i dont think youre an asshole
Varicode: LUL
giovannag: @Cube_Is_Life20 Oh, nice ^^
myaocat: block him too for lols
iamchoco: Any reason for not using python async features? This would seem a good fit
pau1riddle: I would work at Google, though, to be honest :)
geobitz: i think youre like the donald trump of coding but not so narcassitic
Knarez: LUL
joker2k999: then he passed the weed right.. lol
pau1riddle: It's 2019, lol.
myaocat: he said 2018
PhillipWei: the hotness is startups
geobitz: neither is donald trump
TheTastefulToastie: these days it's landing a job at netflix
myaocat: yo im geohot and those who dont know im getting sue by sony B) B) B)
myaocat: are you building backend why no rust/elixir/nodejs? is python better than them?
kanogger: LUL
joker2k999: told ya...
myaocat: rip
myaocat: god you dont know elixir
xyz: LUL
joker2k999: better because you have to think less..
myaocat: how many left to 1m followers?
th3_maj0r: around 990k
th3_maj0r: only 990k*
joker2k999: that back 990k is gonna be a b*tch
steffeKutta: that keyboard sound PogChamp
Yaak0v: that's me alright. always puttin question marks
enlightenedwaterfowl: Header, response body, escaped query param
Cube_Is_Life20: damn George is giving up on instagram already? he just needs to promote it more with his YouTube audience
myaocat: :(
joker2k999: i think all google(recent) employees finish their term, then go and start a youtube channel. interesting cycle... can't say its a bad idea. gotta get that passive income somehow...
Cube_Is_Life20: apparently the alternative to requests is httplib2
joker2k999: doesn't requests always take a while?...
anatoly1974: ping it ??
sadko12: hey
Knarez: fzzPepega
Levent133: hi
sadko12: i wonder if he sees the chat
kanogger: maaaaaTanner maaaaaWhut bleiloHija
Ishaan96: Hi george!!
Cube_Is_Life20: chat is on another screen to our left, if he looks that way then he's reading chat
Markus_47: killall python ^^
anatoly1974: what are u coding Man @georgehotz ??
Cube_Is_Life20: create 100,000 keys and see how it goes?
Cube_Is_Life20: @anatoly1974 read the title of the stream
rage_au: watching this guy is inanse
thisisweeezy: looking great
enlightenedwaterfowl: Rocksdb?
joker2k999: lol
enlightenedwaterfowl: What's your hesitation with Rocks?
BonchPatrol: apache ignite?
Cube_Is_Life20: CodernityDB claims 100,000 get and post requests per second
joker2k999: yea then BOOM. lol
enlightenedwaterfowl: He's looking for an embedded k/v store
enlightenedwaterfowl: (I was an early employee at Ripple. We went through a bunch of embedded DBs)
enlightenedwaterfowl: Rocks is good. Not really sure what your issue with leveldb is though
joker2k999: he's gonna go hit the bong...
MokBeBek: What about Pickle ?
Cube_Is_Life20: zodb allows your multi access
enlightenedwaterfowl: Redis ftw
rage_au: Redis
enlightenedwaterfowl: Probably put it in AOF mode
joker2k999: looks sketchy huh...
DrRobotvinnik: you're my personal maxkeyvalue George <3
rage_au: Redis is crazy good
anatoly1974: MongoDB
Cube_Is_Life20: how long would it take to make your own?
BonchPatrol: put instead of post?
rage_au: his keyboard skills are next level
Markus_47: What keyboard is he using?
Grimonja: didnt return it from Get
Grimonja: Oh well
keepingtrckofthisacct: !uptime
alienware997: Who wants a gift?
gerntt: me
BonchPatrol: yeet me a gift brother
RomanNYC: me :)
joker2k999: theres a joke in there somewhere...
alienware997: i'm going to smoke some and when i came back, there will be gifts!
RomanNYC: PogChamp
gerntt: PogChamp
Twitch0xme: u need apt update && install on same RUN line
keepingtrckofthisacct: what's the uptime, please?
Yaak0v: @keepingtrckofthisacct Current Uptime: 3 hours, 44 minutes, 34 seconds
keepingtrckofthisacct: @Yaak0v thanks
gerntt: 33 days LUL
fowlmoves: Istn it just ADD or COPY?
aresfour: ADD req.txt /path/in/container
aresfour: or COPY
OrdinaryRamblings: @Legonigel sup
fowlmoves: repo update?
fowlmoves: aha
last_pacifist: slam
lefg7: lol
aresfour: Dockers one process per container policy flew out the window lol
murat_kvebekov: @aresfour, it's one program per container :D
murat_kvebekov: not one process
Trenz2: Ariana Grande Kappa
astr0nils: for ariana grande its worth Kappa
TODNESSISBAE: hi
TODNESSISBAE: just wanned to say u are fucking inspiration
Trenz2: you have to follow on instagram to be inspirational :))
aresfour: @murat_kvebekov then they changed it, pretty sure docs used to say one process per container
Trenz2: @georgehotz when u gonna do some ctf's , that was fun :P
alienware997: alienware997 gifted a Tier 1 sub to aresfour! They have given 4 Gift Subs in the channel!
aresfour: ure right, it was changed in 2017 https://github.com/docker/docker.github.io/pull/1418/files
TODNESSISBAE: yea i have
alienware997: alienware997 gifted a Tier 1 sub to Trenz2! They have given 5 Gift Subs in the channel!
Trenz2: ty dude <3
aresfour: thank you @alienware997 <3
Trenz2: u're awsome
na_chaos_Pepega: PogChamp
gerntt: PogChamp
alienware997: alienware997 gifted a Tier 1 sub to RomanNYC! They have given 6 Gift Subs in the channel!
giovannag: PogChamp
RomanNYC: :o
Trenz2: PogChamp
MokBeBek: Do a bash PWD !
Shinnosky: OSFrog OSFrog OSFrog
RomanNYC: thank you!!
keepingtrckofthisacct: everyone's getting subs...cool
Twitch0xme: its just bringup.sh not test/bringup.sh
murat_kvebekov: i thinku should remove test/
murat_kvebekov: and it will work
murat_kvebekov: just bash -c "cd tmp && ./bringup.sh"
murat_kvebekov: now it's other story xD
BobbyFlo: whats up man
murat_kvebekov: the problem in "copy" command was that u added extra slash i think
murat_kvebekov: so bash copied content instead of directory
murat_kvebekov: it self
murat_kvebekov: imho
alienware997: @georgehotz try Kitematic, its a gui for the docker container where you can rename them and much more:)
ActionIsComing: ayyy man
Xavur_: wassup man
Xavur_: How long you been streaming for?
ActionIsComing: !uptime
alienware997: The one who helps solving the porblem in the chat, will get a tier 2 subgift:D
Lazysloth: i hate writing dockerfiles :( so i can't help
ActionIsComing: lol who cares about subgift
oOocouchpotatoOo: that was mean :('
alienware997: @actioniscoming nobody but its funny
Xavur_: he looks tired af
murat_kvebekov: @georgehotz found solution... https://stackoverflow.com/a/37715522/2480216
darkzade: !uptime
Lazysloth: dark there isn't a bot
murat_kvebekov: @darkzade, 4h 16m
murat_kvebekov: ±
darkzade: @murat_kvebekov ty
murat_kvebekov: yw
Xavur_: so he started streaming at midnight? or where is he from
local_root: there you go my g imma sub
local_root: local_root subscribed with Twitch Prime.
Lazysloth: its probably san diego
murat_kvebekov: @xavur_, 22
AlSweigart: 43 raiders from AlSweigart have joined!
alienware997: Why you just not mount/share the filesystem you need with "-v" when you create the Docker Container?
Lazysloth: Kreygasm
alienware997: alienware997 gifted a Tier 2 sub to murat_kvebekov! They have given 7 Gift Subs in the channel!
Lazysloth: no sub emotes i guess we spamming commas , , ,
joker2k999: HeyGuys
Shinnosky: VoteYea
joker2k999: who says garbage code gets written after midnight...
davidsit_site: thought it was garbage in garbage out
joker2k999: sounds like basic. lol
joker2k999: like a boss.
Lazysloth: commit -m "dockerfiles are hard"
joker2k999: Cheers to you Sir.
Trenz2: border 0 , ink 7
LordOfSubs: twitchRaid twitchRaid twitchRaid twitchRaid twitchRaid twitchRaid twitchRaid
Jiggletoes: big peen in the chat
Mua_987410: where?
Jiggletoes: my hand
LordOfSubs: true
Grimonja: Python is just black magic tbh
risky_banana: you ever start coding and then all of a sudden the sun is coming up and you can hear birds and your wife is super pissed off.... ah wait, that's me
joker2k999: im in that club as well ..
LordOfSubs: It sucks that we require sleep
joker2k999: i know! i can't believe someone hasn't solved that problem yet.
LordOfSubs: Meth looked promising, but we know how that turned out...
Lazysloth: i tried to not sleep and nap, it worked but i got bored and lost track of time
joker2k999: facts.
cmanatlan: Modafinil supposedly works, although I wouldn't personally trust it
risky_banana: modafinil will get you there
joker2k999: ..get you somewhere..
Roundlay: Been using it for 10 years, works a treat
joker2k999: *ahem.
Lazysloth: where do you get it?
Roundlay: The pharmacy
cmanatlan: get it prescribed
joker2k999: gasp.
Lazysloth: are you like European?
cmanatlan: i think you can get it prescribed in the US
Roundlay: Expat in Japan
risky_banana: its used for night-shift workers to reset their body clock
cmanatlan: Roundlay oh probably can't in japan
risky_banana: or idiots to stay awake and super focused
risky_banana: either
joker2k999: spy? don't answer that.
Lazysloth: of course japan would have modafinil haha
cmanatlan: oh you're the one who's taking it. can you get modafinil without an Rx in japan? @Roundlay
Roundlay: Not legally
th3_maj0r: lol
Roundlay: But sure
cmanatlan: lol
cmanatlan: meant at a pharmacy
Roundlay: Nope
alienware997: Kratom has become illegal in the US, isn't it?
LordOfSubs: no
joker2k999: chat has gone so left.. lol
LordOfSubs: well some States
quickfloor: bro
lostshiya: @georgehotz I'm an absolute zero in infosec, what's the best place to start?
cmanatlan: joker2k999 what do you mean? how is this discussion even political/social
cmanatlan: we're just asking what drugs are legal :P
joker2k999: LOL.( <--) just means 'it took a turn'..
alienware997: @sheyjoko i thinkthats the wrong place to ask that:)
Grimonja: They just dont want to die D:
cmanatlan: oh you meant it took a left turn?
Knarez: LUL
quickfloor: Why George behind is ordered ? that is not a hacker room :(
alienware997: @quickfloor George likes it clean, like his code xD
Lazysloth: putting stuff in tupperware is ordered?
NMODE: ko1ayPepeV ko1ayPepeV ko1ayPepeV
joker2k999: true.
NMODE: ko1ayPepeV russian hackers ko1ayPepeV
murat_kvebekov: & - needs to be at the end
murat_kvebekov: to make it background gprocess
murat_kvebekov: ow
murat_kvebekov: thanks for sub
murat_kvebekov: didn't realized it
quickfloor: and you guys did you understand something is changed ? yaa that is tmux style
joker2k999: your gonna be later for your coffee chat broSeph
Roundlay: What time is it where George is?
murat_kvebekov: @roundlay, 3 am
EventHorizonxD: look at you go mate
alienware997: @murat_kvebekov no problemo:)
murat_kvebekov: @alienware997, ty :D
Roundlay: O:
murat_kvebekov: @alienware997, was concentrated to what he is doing, and didn't lokked in chat for a while :D
TODNESSISBAE: how long has he been streaming
kanogger: !uptime
joker2k999: !uptime
alienware997: @murat_kvebekov same problem here:D
quickfloor: !followage
murat_kvebekov: 4:50± uptime
TODNESSISBAE: !uptime
Lazysloth: no bot guys, your commands are useless
TODNESSISBAE: lol
murat_kvebekov: @lazysloth, 4h 50m
akbang47: no bot wa du HEck
joker2k999: of course, hackers never use bots
quickfloor: !keyboard
quickfloor: Leopold FC750R
joker2k999: lol
joker2k999: thats cute.
NMODE: we are bots chat MrDestructoid
murat_kvebekov: @quickfloor, 12 nov 2018
murat_kvebekov: @georgehotz for background & - needs to be at end of command
quickfloor: Stackoverflow background is really Ridiculous
Lazysloth: it was april fools, gotta wait till the person managing it wakes up
quickfloor: How does George focus on this keyboard sound? or that is loud for us
NMODE: only this year I found out that fools day is in many countries
myaocat: hack the gibsons
joker2k999: thx for the stream broSki
joker2k999: get them diffs in
quickfloor: u going to Starbucks tomorrow ?
Roundlay: You can change the SE april fools thing with the time icon up top
JonThomasK: whats up george
quickfloor: @georgehotz u picked the best category bro . this is so Basic
myaocat: anyone can explain what is he doing? cant understand
2_kka: Finally caught the stream live, shoutouts to comma ai archive
local_root: !uptime
Shinnosky: !favorite_sushi
Lazysloth: yay passing you may sleep
2_kka: Also wasn’t George’s twitch channel named tomcroose or something before? I thought I had followed the channel in twitch ages ago but the name’s different now
myaocat: hack the planet!!
quickfloor: U won !
Roundlay: gg
JonThomasK: WE DID IT
quickfloor: Good game
Roundlay: <3
TODNESSISBAE: nice
skinzo1998: NO i just got here xd
joker2k999: peace bro
quickfloor: !instagram
anudeepgi: PogChamp
JonThomasK: we instagram famous?
myaocat: thanks for streaming although couldn't watch from statt
joker2k999: more rants bro
Grimonja: Is it 302 redirect? not 307?
Grimonja: Went afk for few hours
PhosphoricAcid: comfy streams
skinzo1998: time difference :( it's ok i'll still watch it on youtube
TODNESSISBAE: when are u going to stream again
PeterBensch: buh bye buh buy, sweet dreams PokPikachu
quickfloor: Angur hoodi ?
2knucklechamp: Please be on tomorrow
2_kka: Quick! Ask about crypto before he’s gone
JonThomasK: ill get qira docker going.. been really busy. @georgehotz
quickfloor: *augur
JonThomasK: bye
quickfloor: Could qira be secend ida pro :D ?
joker2k999: yea docker gets good. good tool for the tool box
TODNESSISBAE: bye
pau1riddle: peace
th3_maj0r: peaceee
2_kka: Later George
Atxpert: i just got in :(
ggwpl2p: bye dude
myaocat: bb
Shinnosky: Grey hoodie cheerrr uuuup
anudeepgi: bye
TODNESSISBAE: when are u going to stream again
Grimonja: Yea i did but on Readme it said 302
alienware997: Bb:) good night:)
myaocat: hack the planet!!
Grimonja: So just syaing
joker2k999: lol
Trenz2: have a nice one man !
JonThomasK: "Fuck off with the crypto"... new band name
Shinnosky: U right
ggwpl2p: lmao
TODNESSISBAE: legend
myaocat: hack the planet
myaocat: hack the planet!
joker2k999: he turned into Confucius there at the end. lol